frontrush.com 2018-03-04

# Front Rush::Privacy Policy

#### FRONT RUSH PRIVACY POLICY

######### Effective October 21, 2016

Welcome to the digital services offered by Front Rush LLC (“Front Rush”, “we”, “us” or “our”). Front Rush respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy tells you how we will use the information entrusted to us when you visit https://www.frontrush.com, https://www.coachpacket.com, https://recruitspot.com, and any other online site or mobile application that links to this Privacy Policy (collectively the “Services”). Unless a customer has a separate agreement with Front Rush that governs his/her use of the Front Rush web and mobile based application software, this Privacy Policy also applies to the content that customers store on our system, including any personal information.

##### Collection of Information

We collect or receive the following general types of information when you use the Services:

Information You Provide Directly. You may provide information directly to us through the Services in several different ways. For example, you may respond to specific questions, communicate with us via email or feedback forms, complete online registration forms or questionnaires, and subscribe to email newsletters or other similar communications. The types of information you may provide directly include the following, as applicable:

  * Name;
  * Street address;
  * Email address;
  * Telephone number;
  * Date of birth/age;
  * Height/weight;
  * Gender;
  * Photograph;
  * Occupation;
  * Athletic information (e.g., sport and position);
  * School;
  * Graduation Year;
  * Academic information (e.g., GPA, SAT/ACT score, awards/honors, and extracurricular activities);
  * Payment information (e.g., credit card number and debit card number);
  * User ID;
  * Password; and
  * Other relevant information.

Information We Collect Automatically. We collect certain information about you and your computer automatically when you use the Services. Automatically collected information may include:

  * The type of web browser and operating system you have used to access the Services;

  * Your IP address (which is a number automatically assigned to your computer when you access the Internet and can be used to derive your general geographic location);

  * Your device information (which may include information about the mobile device you use to access our mobile application, including the hardware model, operating system and version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information);

  * The website you visited before you came to the Services; and

  * Information about the content and webpages you view, clickstream patterns, dates and times that the Services are accessed, and the features you access on the Services that we collect using cookies, Web beacons, and similar technologies.

Social Networking Information. If applicable, you log in to the Services through a social networking account (e.g., Facebook), we may collect information about you from that social networking account, including your name, email address, birthday, profile photograph, and other information associated with your social networking account.

Information from Commercially Available Sources. We may receive additional information about you from other sources, such as data cooperatives and public databases.

We may combine all of the information we collect or receive about you and use or disclose it in the manner described in this Privacy Policy.

##### Use of Information

We use the information we collect and receive for the following general purposes:

  * To provide you with the Services, products, and information you request and with legal notices or information about changes to this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use;

  * To perform analytics to continually improve the Services and enhance your experience with the Services;

  * To provide you (and enable our partners to provide you) with promotional materials, relevant content and advertisements, surveys, newsletters, questionnaires, and other materials;

  * To offer you information regarding certain products and services of our partners, sponsors, advertisers, and affiliates;

  * To manage your account, perform billing and payment activities, and update you on your account status (including confirmation of registrations or notices of subscription expiration);

  * To respond to your requests, questions, and comments;

  * As we believe is necessary to protect our rights and the rights of others, including by enforcing our Terms of Use; and

  * For any other purpose disclosed to you at the time we collect your information, or pursuant to your consent.

You may “opt out” of receiving promotional communications from Front Rush by contacting us at the email address shown at the end of this Privacy Policy. Please note that changing your information through your user profile settings, or otherwise opting out of receipt of communications from Front Rush, will only change or delete the data for purposes of future activities on our website and for managing future communications from Front Rush.

##### Sharing of Information

We may share your information with the following entities:

Colleges and Other Users of the Services. We may share your information directly with educational institutions, college coaches, and athletic directors. The Services may also provide opportunities for you and other users to connect with each other socially and to view each other’s profiles. To achieve this, certain information you provide may be shared with other users of the Services.

Affiliates. We may share your information with our affiliates—companies that control, are controlled by, or are under common control with, Front Rush. These entities may use your information to make predictions about your interests and may provide you with offers, promotional materials, advertisements, and other materials.

Partners. We may share your information with partners who provide products or services that may be of interest to you or college athletes, including: (i) educational products and services (e.g., colleges, student loans, financial aid, college admissions and tutorial services, and extra-curricular enrichment and recognition programs); (ii) career, employment, and military opportunities; (iii) products of consumer focused companies; (iv) recruiting services; (v) sports related activities; and (v) other relevant products and services. These partners may use your information to make predictions about your interests and may provide you with offers, promotional materials, advertisements, and other materials. We also may share your information with partners, such as Chegg, Cappex, and NRCCUA, that share your information with college admissions departments.

Service Providers. We also may share your information with entities that provide services to us, including companies that provide payment processing, shipping, web analytics, data processing, web hosting, technical support, advertising, email distribution, and other services.

Other Parties When Required by Law or as Necessary to Protect Our Services. There may be instances when we disclose your information to other parties in order to:

  * protect the legal rights of Front Rush, its affiliates, and of the users of the Services;
  * protect the safety and security of users of the Services;
  * prevent fraud (or for risk management purposes); or
  * comply with or respond to the law or legal process or a request for cooperation by a government entity, whether or not legally required.

Other Parties in Aggregated Form. We may also share your information with third parties in aggregated or non-personally identifiable form.

Other Parties in Connection With a Transfer of Assets. If we make a sale or transfer of assets, or are otherwise involved in a merger, divestiture, acquisition, liquidation, or transfer, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy, we may transfer your information to one or more third parties as part of that transaction.

Other Parties With Your Consent. In addition to the sharing described in this Privacy Policy, we may share information about you with other third parties when you consent to such sharing.

If you do not want your information shared with any third party who may use such information for direct marketing purposes, then you  may opt out of such disclosures by sending an email to us at privacy@frontrush.com.

##### Third-Party Functionality

Some of the functionality of the Services may be provided by third parties that are not affiliated with Front Rush. These entities may collect or receive certain information about your use of the Services, including through the use of cookies, Web beacons, and similar technologies. Front Rush is not responsible for the privacy practices of these entities.

##### Protection of Information

We use reasonable physical and technical measures to safeguard information in our possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure, or modification. Please note, however, that no data transmission or storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect the information we maintain, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Services, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask that you not share your password with anyone.

##### Children’s Information

The Services are intended for a general audience and are not directed at children younger than 13. We do not knowingly collect or store personal information about children under the age of 13 without parental consent, unless permitted by law.

##### Non-U.S. Users

The Services are intended for a U.S. audience. If you access the Services from outside the United States, please be aware that information you provide to us or that we obtain as a result of your use of the Services may be processed and transferred to the United States and be subject to U.S. law. The privacy and data protection laws in the United States may not be equivalent to such laws in your country of residence. By using our website, participating in any of the Services, or by providing us with your information, you consent to the collection, transfer, storage, and processing of information to and in the United States.

##### Changing or Deleting Your Personal Information

We wish to maintain accurate personal information. If you have submitted personal information through our website and set-up an account, then you can (i) access and update your personal information by logging into your online account and making the appropriate changes or (ii) delete your account by email us at privacy@frontrush.com. Please note that if you delete your account, we may continue to retain your information on our servers for archival purposes. If you have forgotten your login credentials, you can retrieve those via our automated password retrieval system.

##### Targeted Advertising

In some cases, we and advertisers on the Services work with other third-party vendors to help deliver advertisements targeted to your interests. These vendors include ad networks and analytics providers, and they use cookies or other technologies to collect information about your online activity (e.g., the sites and pages you have visited) in order to help advertisers deliver particular ads that they believe you would find most relevant. Many third-party vendors that perform these functions are members of the Network Advertising Initiative or the Digital Advertising Alliance, and you can opt out of those vendors’ delivery of targeted advertising to you by visiting http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp and http://www.aboutads.info/choices/.

Please note that, because these opt-out tools will place a cookie on your computer to record your opt-out preference, any actions you take using these tools will apply only to the web browser that you use to take the action. Also, these tools may not work as expected if you set your browser to refuse cookies.

Sometimes, our advertisers will contract with a third-party service to host their ads. In this case, an ad-serving vendor contacts the advertisers’ hosting service to obtain a particular advertisement. Because we do not have a relationship with these third parties, we do not have a mechanism to allow visitors to opt out of tracking by these vendors.

##### Cookies, Web Beacons, and Similar Technologies

Front Rush—as well as certain third parties that provide content and other functionality on the Services—may use a variety of technologies to learn more about how people use the Services and the Internet. This section provides more information about some of those technologies and how they work.

Cookies. Cookies are small text files that websites and other online services use to store information about users on the users’ own computers. For example, cookies can be used to store your sign-in credentials so that you do not have to enter them each time you return to a website. Cookies also may be used to store a unique identification number tied to your computer so that a website can recognize you as the same user across different visits to the website. You can configure your Internet browser to warn you each time a cookie is being sent or to refuse cookies completely.

Front Rush and the third parties that provide content or functionality on the Services may use cookies to:

  * Collect information about your browsing activities in order to provide you with more relevant content and ads off the Services; and

  * Relate the information automatically collected when you use the Services to information we obtain from you directly or from commercially available sources.

Other local storage. We, along with third-party partners, may use other kinds of local storage, such as Local Shared Objects (also referred to as “Flash cookies”) and HTML5 local storage, in connection with the Services. These technologies are similar to the cookies discussed above in that they are stored on your computer and can be used to store certain information about your activities and preferences. These objects are stored in different parts of your computer from ordinary browser cookies, however. Many Internet browsers allow you to disable HTML5 local storage or delete information contained in HTML5 local storage using browser controls.

Web beacons. We, along with our third-party partners, may also use technologies called Web beacons that communicate information from your Internet browser to a web server. Web beacons can be embedded in web pages, videos, or emails, and can allow a web server to read certain types of information from your browser, check whether you have viewed a particular web page or email message, and determine, among other things, the time and date on which you viewed the Web beacon, the IP address of your computer, and the URL of the web page from which the Web beacon was viewed. We and our partners use Web beacons for a variety of purposes, including analyzing the use of the Services and in conjunction with cookies to provide content and ads that are more relevant to you.

##### Your California Privacy Rights

California residents are entitled once a year, free of charge, to request and obtain certain information regarding our disclosure of certain categories of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request to: 

Attn: Front Rush Privacy   
Front Rush LLC   
62 South Main Street   
Yardley, PA 19067   
Email: privacy@frontrush.com 

In addition, California residents who are registered users of the Services and are under the age of 18 are entitled, in accordance with California law, to request and obtain removal of content and information that they themselves post as user content on the Services. You may request such removal by emailing us at privacy@frontrush.com. Please note that your request does not ensure the complete or comprehensive removal of the material.

##### Do Not Track Signal

Some web browsers may transmit “do-not-track” signals to the websites with which the user communicates. We do not currently take action in response to those signals. If an industry standard on responding to such signals is established and accepted, we may reassess how to respond to those signals.

##### Links to Other Websites

Our website may contain links or references to third-party owned and/or operated websites that we believe might be of interest to users, including websites of our partners, sponsors, advertisers, and affiliates. We do not control the content of these third-party websites. These third-party websites may send you their own cookies, collect data, or solicit personal information. Once you have clicked on a link to a third-party website and leave our website, you must read the privacy policy of the third-party website to see how your personal information will be handled.

##### Changes to this Privacy Policy

From time to time, we may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect changes to the scope of the Services or for other reasons. Therefore, it is important to check the effective date of the Privacy Policy posted here each time you use the Services. If we make any material revisions to this Privacy Policy, we will email you at the email address you have provided or will place a notice on our website. By continuing to use the Services after we make changes, you indicate your consent to those changes.

##### Questions and Contact Information

We want to assure you that we are dedicated to protecting your privacy. If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: 

Attn: Front Rush Privacy   
Front Rush LLC   
62 South Main Street   
Yardley, PA 19067   
Email: privacy@frontrush.com
